[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "I mean it should be technically, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "should", "be", "technically", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Winklevoss is fine.", "answer_tokens": ["Winklevoss", "is", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "That must have been weird, wasn't it, watching one guy play both of you?", "question_tokens": ["That", "must", "have", "been", "weird", ",", "was", "n't", "it", ",", "watching", "one", "guy", "play", "both", "of", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "CD", "NN", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, it was definitely -- we had to remind ourselves, even though we knew that there were some CGI effects and -- after a while, you're watching the movie and you kind of forget that it's one guy playing two people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "definitely", "--", "we", "had", "to", "remind", "ourselves", ",", "even", "though", "we", "knew", "that", "there", "were", "some", "CGI", "effects", "and", "--", "after", "a", "while", ",", "you", "'re", "watching", "the", "movie", "and", "you", "kind", "of", "forget", "that", "it", "'s", "one", "guy", "playing", "two", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Did you want to go and see it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "want", "to", "go", "and", "see", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "There's definitely a lot of uncertainty.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "definitely", "a", "lot", "of", "uncertainty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "How is that different from MySpace or Friendster?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "that", "different", "from", "MySpace", "or", "Friendster", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Harvard.edu.", "answer_tokens": ["Harvard.edu", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Friendster"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Honestly?", "question_tokens": ["Honestly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "There's so many things to think.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "so", "many", "things", "to", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Horrible?", "question_tokens": ["Horrible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "We see --", "answer_tokens": ["We", "see", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "We certainly see a person who is where he is today absolutely because we approached him with our idea, our business plan, and two years of worth of work.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "certainly", "see", "a", "person", "who", "is", "where", "he", "is", "today", "absolutely", "because", "we", "approached", "him", "with", "our", "idea", ",", "our", "business", "plan", ",", "and", "two", "years", "of", "worth", "of", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Sure, I mean he's intelligent.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "I", "mean", "he", "'s", "intelligent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Didn't he just come along and go, I really like that idea, but I've got a better one?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "he", "just", "come", "along", "and", "go", ",", "I", "really", "like", "that", "idea", ",", "but", "I", "'ve", "got", "a", "better", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "A cheat?", "question_tokens": ["A", "cheat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "That's one way of putting it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "one", "way", "of", "putting", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "The guy that looks over your shoulder and nicks some of your best lines?", "question_tokens": ["The", "guy", "that", "looks", "over", "your", "shoulder", "and", "nicks", "some", "of", "your", "best", "lines", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "What we agreed to and what we got are two different things.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "we", "agreed", "to", "and", "what", "we", "got", "are", "two", "different", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "And is that part of our ongoing dispute, then?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "that", "part", "of", "our", "ongoing", "dispute", ",", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "I mean if the company is worth X billion dollars and, you know, people decided you were telling the truth, and your idea had been stolen, why didn't you get $4 billion?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "the", "company", "is", "worth", "X", "billion", "dollars", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "decided", "you", "were", "telling", "the", "truth", ",", "and", "your", "idea", "had", "been", "stolen", ",", "why", "did", "n't", "you", "get", "$", "4", "billion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["X billion dollars", "$4 billion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Is he -- again, devil's advocate, I mean, aren't you guys also just in this for the money now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "--", "again", ",", "devil", "'s", "advocate", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "guys", "also", "just", "in", "this", "for", "the", "money", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, this is a very principled --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "a", "very", "principled", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Why don't you let it go?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "let", "it", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "It's a good question, I understand that sentiment.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "good", "question", ",", "I", "understand", "that", "sentiment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "It's not about money for you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "about", "money", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, it -- money is inextricably tied to the principle.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "--", "money", "is", "inextricably", "tied", "to", "the", "principle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "What's more important?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "more", "important", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Both have to be -- I'll tell you why both are important.", "answer_tokens": ["Both", "have", "to", "be", "--", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "why", "both", "are", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Were you one-hit wonders?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "one-hit", "wonders", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBD", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, w happened was that when Mark launched the Facebook, when we were completely blindsided by it, we launched our site later, but because of the damage, we were late to market.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "w", "happened", "was", "that", "when", "Mark", "launched", "the", "Facebook", ",", "when", "we", "were", "completely", "blindsided", "by", "it", ",", "we", "launched", "our", "site", "later", ",", "but", "because", "of", "the", "damage", ",", "we", "were", "late", "to", "market", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Have you had another great idea?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "another", "great", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "We've got a couple of ideas in the works.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "got", "a", "couple", "of", "ideas", "in", "the", "works", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Or are you worried about me stealing it?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "you", "worried", "about", "me", "stealing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "How is that doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "that", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "It's doing well.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "doing", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What's it worth do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "worth", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "I'd say probably in the millions.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", "probably", "in", "the", "millions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "But you go to Harvard, you get trained to be an attack dog in business?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "go", "to", "Harvard", ",", "you", "get", "trained", "to", "be", "an", "attack", "dog", "in", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harvard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Isn't just attack dog speak?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "just", "attack", "dog", "speak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Within the rules.", "answer_tokens": ["Within", "the", "rules", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Harvard"], "PERSON": ["Mark Zuckerberg"]}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Did that moment happen?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "moment", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "In effect we did, we first learned about Facebook and Mark Zuckerberg launching it by reading the Harvard student newspaper.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "effect", "we", "did", ",", "we", "first", "learned", "about", "Facebook", "and", "Mark", "Zuckerberg", "launching", "it", "by", "reading", "the", "Harvard", "student", "newspaper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "And what was your first reaction?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "your", "first", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "We were pretty shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "pretty", "shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"]}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to him?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "spoke", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "We spoke to him at the mediation in 2008.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "spoke", "to", "him", "at", "the", "mediation", "in", "2008", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "You haven't spoken to him in, what, three years?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "n't", "spoken", "to", "him", "in", ",", "what", ",", "three", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Why should I care?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "I", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "He clearly at this moment doesn't care.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "clearly", "at", "this", "moment", "does", "n't", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "You think so?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "He hasn't any of that?", "question_tokens": ["He", "has", "n't", "any", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Have you read to that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "read", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "First of all, we got screwed because we place trust and confidence in a partner.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "we", "got", "screwed", "because", "we", "place", "trust", "and", "confidence", "in", "a", "partner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 299, "question": "What do you think of Eduardo?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Eduardo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "In what --", "answer_tokens": ["In", "what", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Did he get screwed as well do you think or not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "get", "screwed", "as", "well", "do", "you", "think", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "How much did he end up with?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "did", "he", "end", "up", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "We don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eduardo"]}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Again I say to you, I mean, how sorry are we supposed to feel for you guys?", "question_tokens": ["Again", "I", "say", "to", "you", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "how", "sorry", "are", "we", "supposed", "to", "feel", "for", "you", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Well, that's a different -- we shouldn't be conflated with Eduardo.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "different", "--", "we", "should", "n't", "be", "conflated", "with", "Eduardo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Do you use Facebook?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "use", "Facebook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Quite ironic, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Quite", "ironic", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Not as ironic if we weren't on it because again --", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "as", "ironic", "if", "we", "were", "n't", "on", "it", "because", "again", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "How do you work that out?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "work", "that", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, we worked that out because the guys who -- who originated the idea would be -- you would think that would be the ones who would be able to take part in it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "worked", "that", "out", "because", "the", "guys", "who", "--", "who", "originated", "the", "idea", "would", "be", "--", "you", "would", "think", "that", "would", "be", "the", "ones", "who", "would", "be", "able", "to", "take", "part", "in", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "How many friends do you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "friends", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "It's north of 1,000.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "north", "of", "1,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Who's got more?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "got", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Tyler.", "answer_tokens": ["Tyler", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Just more diligent at it.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "more", "diligent", "at", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Nicer guy?", "question_tokens": ["Nicer", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Maybe.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Who gets more women?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "gets", "more", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "That's a tough question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "tough", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "I mean they must be cueing up, are they?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "they", "must", "be", "cueing", "up", ",", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, but back to we got all of this money.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "but", "back", "to", "we", "got", "all", "of", "this", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Piers, it's dangerous to make assumptions about anybody's life.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "dangerous", "to", "make", "assumptions", "about", "anybody", "'s", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What's the future going to hold for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "future", "going", "to", "hold", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, the immediate future is training for London 2012.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "immediate", "future", "is", "training", "for", "London", "2012", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "And can you win there?", "question_tokens": ["And", "can", "you", "win", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "We're going to try.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What do you do if Mark Zuckerberg suddenly pops up in a rival boat that's just a little bit better than yours?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "if", "Mark", "Zuckerberg", "suddenly", "pops", "up", "in", "a", "rival", "boat", "that", "'s", "just", "a", "little", "bit", "better", "than", "yours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "As long as -- again as long as it's fair play --", "answer_tokens": ["As", "long", "as", "--", "again", "as", "long", "as", "it", "'s", "fair", "play", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Zuckerberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Are you going to sue him?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "sue", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "How often do you think about him a day?", "question_tokens": ["How", "often", "do", "you", "think", "about", "him", "a", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Not -- I mean, I think we've done a very good job of compartmentalizing.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'ve", "done", "a", "very", "good", "job", "of", "compartmentalizing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "It's not a bad career, though, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "bad", "career", ",", "though", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I wouldn't call it a career.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "call", "it", "a", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "How much money do you want?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "money", "do", "you", "want", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "What we want is a fair resolution.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "we", "want", "is", "a", "fair", "resolution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "How much do you want?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "want", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Well, it's not what we have now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "what", "we", "have", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", ":"], "qSentId": 459, "question": "$100 million?", "question_tokens": ["$", "100", "million", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "A mediation where --", "answer_tokens": ["A", "mediation", "where", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$100 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Two hundred?", "question_tokens": ["Two", "hundred", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "We're not going to -- we're not going to answer that question.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "--", "we", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "answer", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "$65 million?", "question_tokens": ["$", "65", "million", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$65 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "No one wants to hear anymore about Mark and you think, how much?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "wants", "to", "hear", "anymore", "about", "Mark", "and", "you", "think", ",", "how", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "We're reasonable people.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "reasonable", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "If I invite Mark Zuckerberg on this show with you, would you come on?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "invite", "Mark", "Zuckerberg", "on", "this", "show", "with", "you", ",", "would", "you", "come", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Zuckerberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Final question, do you have the public are on your side or on Mark Zuckerberg's?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "question", ",", "do", "you", "have", "the", "public", "are", "on", "your", "side", "or", "on", "Mark", "Zuckerberg", "'s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I think the public doesn't know the complete story yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "public", "does", "n't", "know", "the", "complete", "story", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Zuckerberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "That's not true, is it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "true", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "No, it's not true.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Where do you think that you're different from that character that was portrayed in the film?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "that", "you", "'re", "different", "from", "that", "character", "that", "was", "portrayed", "in", "the", "film", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I'm -- you know, a better personality.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--", "you", "know", ",", "a", "better", "personality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Do they?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I have to tell time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "tell", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Need to be able to tell time, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Need", "to", "be", "able", "to", "tell", "time", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "You say you beat the odds.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "say", "you", "beat", "the", "odds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tuohy"]}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "How did you beat the odds?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "beat", "the", "odds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "You know, coming from where I came from, you know, the environment I was in, you know, being taken in by my family, the Tuohy family, that doesn't happen every day.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "coming", "from", "where", "I", "came", "from", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "environment", "I", "was", "in", ",", "you", "know", ",", "being", "taken", "in", "by", "my", "family", ",", "the", "Tuohy", "family", ",", "that", "does", "n't", "happen", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "So how much do you think you owe the Tuohys?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "much", "do", "you", "think", "you", "owe", "the", "Tuohys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I owe them quite a bit, because they didn't have to do what they did, taking somebody in to their family, you know, coming from where I came from.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "owe", "them", "quite", "a", "bit", ",", "because", "they", "did", "n't", "have", "to", "do", "what", "they", "did", ",", "taking", "somebody", "in", "to", "their", "family", ",", "you", "know", ",", "coming", "from", "where", "I", "came", "from", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "You think you would have made it anyway?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "you", "would", "have", "made", "it", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "The road would have been a little bit tougher, but, you know, growing up, I always said that -- you know, since I was 13, I'm going to get out.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "road", "would", "have", "been", "a", "little", "bit", "tougher", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "growing", "up", ",", "I", "always", "said", "that", "--", "you", "know", ",", "since", "I", "was", "13", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "get", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "You were not going to be sucked down by the system you were born into?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "not", "going", "to", "be", "sucked", "down", "by", "the", "system", "you", "were", "born", "into", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "No, I was not going to be a cycle.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "not", "going", "to", "be", "a", "cycle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "What percentage of kids that you grew up with got out?", "question_tokens": ["What", "percentage", "of", "kids", "that", "you", "grew", "up", "with", "got", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Right now, I'm the only one.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "I", "'m", "the", "only", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "If you were telling me how tough it's been, what were the toughest moments for you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "telling", "me", "how", "tough", "it", "'s", "been", ",", "what", "were", "the", "toughest", "moments", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "You know, like you say, you never understand it fully.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "like", "you", "say", ",", "you", "never", "understand", "it", "fully", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "You know, some things you have to force yourself to, you know, put behind you in order to move on.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "some", "things", "you", "have", "to", "force", "yourself", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "put", "behind", "you", "in", "order", "to", "move", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "The baby was killed?", "question_tokens": ["The", "baby", "was", "killed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "If I remember, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "remember", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Do you talk to her anymore?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "talk", "to", "her", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "You know, the relationships -- you know, it's not like it used to be.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "relationships", "--", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "like", "it", "used", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Do you think that was the root of all the problems for her?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "was", "the", "root", "of", "all", "the", "problems", "for", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "You know, I -- she was a product of her environment.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "she", "was", "a", "product", "of", "her", "environment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "What do you think she thinks of your success now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "she", "thinks", "of", "your", "success", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I really don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "But she hasn't told you that?", "question_tokens": ["But", "she", "has", "n't", "told", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "I never heard it from her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "heard", "it", "from", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Why did you stop talking?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "stop", "talking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "You know, after you try to help a person for so long, you know, they have to want to help them self.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "after", "you", "try", "to", "help", "a", "person", "for", "so", "long", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "have", "to", "want", "to", "help", "them", "self", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "''", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Do you remember the first time you heard those words?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "the", "first", "time", "you", "heard", "those", "words", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "No, she said it a number of times before I finally told her \"I love you\" back.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "she", "said", "it", "a", "number", "of", "times", "before", "I", "finally", "told", "her", "``", "I", "love", "you", "''", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Or do you find it hard?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "find", "it", "hard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "It will always be hard for me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "will", "always", "be", "hard", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "You went to see it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "went", "to", "see", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Yeah, I saw the movie.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "saw", "the", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "What was that like, weird?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", ",", "weird", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "You know, yeah, in a fact, because people don't have a movie made about them every day.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "yeah", ",", "in", "a", "fact", ",", "because", "people", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "movie", "made", "about", "them", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "You don't get that every day, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "get", "that", "every", "day", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "That's zero out of a billion.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "zero", "out", "of", "a", "billion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "Have you met Sandra?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "Sandra", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "I haven't met any of them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "met", "any", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Did she?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "She loved it.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "loved", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "That's got to be a dream come true, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "got", "to", "be", "a", "dream", "come", "true", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "She's starting to take on the personality in the movie, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "starting", "to", "take", "on", "the", "personality", "in", "the", "movie", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "Has it damaged your relationship with the Tuohys at all, the attention, the movie, the books, and everything?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "damaged", "your", "relationship", "with", "the", "Tuohys", "at", "all", ",", "the", "attention", ",", "the", "movie", ",", "the", "books", ",", "and", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "What would you say to them to try and achieve what you've achieved?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "them", "to", "try", "and", "achieve", "what", "you", "'ve", "achieved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "You know, I just want to send a message out that you don't have to be saved by a wealthy white family.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "just", "want", "to", "send", "a", "message", "out", "that", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "be", "saved", "by", "a", "wealthy", "white", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "You still want to beat him, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "still", "want", "to", "beat", "him", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "I play him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "play", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "As the rose between two thorns in this particular interview, what were they like, these two, to work for, these two heavily egoed movie stars?", "question_tokens": ["As", "the", "rose", "between", "two", "thorns", "in", "this", "particular", "interview", ",", "what", "were", "they", "like", ",", "these", "two", ",", "to", "work", "for", ",", "these", "two", "heavily", "egoed", "movie", "stars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "DT", "CD", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "CD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "Well, they talk a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "talk", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]